cheatbook.de 2017-06-06

# Cheatbook Privacy Statement

---|---  
|  |   
| |   
|  |   
| |   
 | The encyclopedia of game cheats. A die hard gamer would get pissed if they saw someone using cheats and walkthroughs in games, but you have to agree, sometimes little hint or the "God Mode" becomes necessary to beat a particularly hard part of the game. If you're an avid gamer and want a few extra weapons and tools the survive the game, CheatBook DataBase is exactly the resource you would want. Find even secrets on our [page.](http://www.cheatbook.de/privacy.htm) |   
| |   
|  |   
| |   
| 

## **Privacy Policy**

|   
| |   
|  |   |   
---|---  
  |    
  |  **Notice:**  
  | We guarantee to provide our visitors with the choice of future site contact and dissemination of non-aggregate personal information to third parties.  
  |    
  |  **Choice:**  
  | We guarantee to provide our visitors with the choice of future site contact and dissemination of non-aggregate personal information to third parties.  
  |    
  |  **Access:**  
  | We guarantee to disclose information protection during transmission and subsequent storage.  
  |    
  |  **Security:**  
  | We guarantee to disclose information protection during transmission and subsequent storage.  
  |    
  |  **Links:**  
  | This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Cheatbook is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this Web site.  
  |    
  |  **Contact:**  
  | We guarantee to allow submission of private questions and alternative complaints from organization.  
  | If you have any other question feel free to **e-mail** us: [**Contact form**](http://www.cheatbook.de/contact.htm)  
   
| |   
 |  |    
  
  |  |    
---|---|---  
| 

|   
 |  |    
  |  |    
 |  |    
| |   
| **Top Games:**   [Outlast 2 Trainer](http://blog.cheatbook.de/outlast-2-trainer/ "Outlast 2 Trainer")  |  [Endless Space 2 Trainer](http://blog.cheatbook.de/endless-space-2-trainer/ "Endless Space 2 Trainer")  |  [Battlefield 1 Trainer](http://blog.cheatbook.de/battlefield-1-trainer/ "Battlefield 1 Trainer")  |  [Dead Rising 4 Trainer](http://blog.cheatbook.de/dead-rising-4-trainer/ "Dead Rising 4 Trainer")  |  [Mass Effect: Andromeda Trainer](http://blog.cheatbook.de/mass-effect-andromeda-trainer/ "Mass Effect: Andromeda Trainer")  |  [Titanfall 2 Trainer](http://blog.cheatbook.de/titanfall-2-trainer/ "Titanfall 2 Trainer") |
